A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Albums, RG 2 FA1128A FA1128A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Small, 1940-1989; 2
  - 000 - Art, 1980s; 1
    - 000-3, Art and New York houses, 1980s; Miniature album with 3x5 color snapshots (Box A 82)
      Flowers, artwork, 834 and Kent House; LSR, MFR, family, unidentified guests, dog. (LSR Album Accession number 219.)
    - 000-4, Art (Kent House), 1982 October; Miniature album with 3x5 color snapshots (Box A 82)
      Also Philipsburg Manor meeting, LR, Fred Smith. (LSR Album Accession number 32.)
    - 000-5, Valley Ranch House, 1982 April; Miniature album with 3x5 color snapshots (Box A 82)
      Rugs; MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 146.)
    - 000-6, Valley Ranch House, 1982 April; Miniature album with 3x5 color snapshots (Box A 82)
      Rugs. (LSR Album Accession number 29.)
  - 100 - Family, 1940-1989; 2
    - 100-1, Daughters, MFR with girls, circa 1940 (Box A 83)
      One photo with dog (Sentry); photos by Lena Towsley. (LSR Album Accession number 33.)
    - 100-2, Daughters, with MFR and LSR, circa 1942 (Box A 83)
      Photos by Lena Towsley.(LSR Album Accession number 34.)
    - 100-3, Children, with MFR, circa 1945; 5 x7 graytone, photos attached together in an accordian fold (Box A 83)
      Formal individual portraits and one group portrait. (LSR Album Accession number 35.)
    - 100-4, MFR and girls at beach and at zoo; LSR children at birthday party; wedding; girls opening presents, 1940s; Black and white, mainly 5x7 prints. (Box A 83)
      Includes some photos with LSR. Wedding - possibly that of John French and Eleanor Clark. (LSR Album Accession number 38.)
    - 100-5, circa 1949 and earlier; black and white, 5x7 (Box A 83)
      JDR Jr. Family Christmas portrait; formal family gathering with JDR Jr. and sons posed portraits; children's birthday party; formal Christmas dinner with AAR; LSR children decorating tree and opening presents; MFR and French family. (LSR Album Accession number 2.)
    - 100-6, LSR and MFR Christmas Cards, 1947-1989; Album overfull; some cards interleaved; some pageholders deteriorated (Box A 84)
      Cards sent; some years missing. (LSR Album Accession number 42.)
    - 100-7, LSR and MFR with children: Golden Gate Bridge; JY Ranch, 1950s; Black and white 5x7. Ring bound album; spine broken. (Box A 84)
      LSR Album Accession number 39.
    - 100-9, Wedding of Laura Rockefeller and James H. Case III, 1956 June 14; Only 4 photos, black and white (6x8 and 3x4). (Box A 84)
      LSR Album Accession number 47.
    - 100-10, French Family picnics, 1957-1982; Color, mainly 5x7. Color yellowing in some photos. (Box A 85)
      Group photos; include LSR and MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 203.)
    - 100-14, Wedding of Lucy Rockefeller and Charles Hamlin, 1964 June 13; Album embossed LAR-CH and date; pages split and adhesive deteriorated; only 6 color 5x7 photos. (Box A 85)
      6 photos only, include LSR and Lucy; reception. (LSR Album Accession number 218.)
    - 100-16, Wedding of Marion French Rockefeller and Warren Titus Weber, 1965 June 12; Very full album, black and white and color, 5x7 prints. (Box A 86)
      Wedding at Woodstock; formal and informal portraits; NAR, JDR 3, LSR, MFR, family and guests. (LSR Album Accession number 201.)
    - 100-17, Laura and James Case and Family, 1966-1968; Color and black and white, 3x5 photos. (Box A 86)
      Includes several photos of Red and Belle Mathews; at JY Ranch, snowmobiling and Woodstock in winter. (LSR Album Accession number 194.)
    - 100-18, Wedding of Lucy Rockefeller and Jeremy Waletzky, 1970 June 27; 5x7 color prints. (Box A 87)
      Family pictures, including NAR, Case children. (LSR Album Accession number 206.)
    - 100-19, 1970s; 5x7 color prints. Very full 3-ring album. Adhesive on edges of page holders deteriorated - page protectors cracking open. (Box A 87)
      Family and friends: LSR, MFR, and family at JY; Lady Bird Johnson, Kenneth Chorley, and others at JY; LSR and MFR in Polynesia, Caribbean, Sea Star, with family; French Family reunion, September 1973; LSR (with Albright or Fabian) at JY. (LSR Album Accession number 200.)
    - 100-20, "Jacob's World", 1974; Five color 5x7 photos. (Box A 88)
      LSR Album Accession number 17.
    - 100-21, Rockefeller Family Christmas Dinner at Kykuit, 1976 December; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 88)
      Several photos of NAR; individual and group shots. (LSR Album Accession number 44.)
    - 100-22, LSR, MFR, Waletzky family at Caneel Bay at Christmas, 1978 December; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 88)
      Album entitled "Caneel Bay, Christmas 1978." (LSR Album Accession number 43.)
    - 100-23, LSR and MFR Anniversary party at JY, with children and grandchildren, 1980 August 15; Mainly black and white 3x5 photos. Flip album, pages detaching - Should be removed from album and copied to preserve order (Box A 89)
      Album entitled "Happy Annivirthday, MFR LSR, JY, August, 1980." A few photos of the party, but mainly group and individual photos. Also photos of Red and Belle Mathews. (LSR Album Accession number 45.)
    - 100-25, Jacob and Naomi Waletzky with MFR, circa 1981-1982; Miniature album, 12 color 3x5 photos (Box A 89)
      Also Lucy and Jeremy Waletzky. (LSR Album Accession number 220.)
    - 100-26, Children and grandchildren at JY, 1981-1982; 5x7 mainly color (Box A 89)
      LSR Album Accession number 40.
    - 100-27, Peter and Matthew Case, 1984; Miniature album, 11 color 3x5 photos (Box A 89)
      At JY, Album labeled "1982" but photos are dated 1984. (LSR Album Accession number 199.)
  - 200 - Houses, 1940s - 1980s; 3
    - 200-N1, Catskills House, 1980 September; Color 3x5 prints in flip album. (Box A 90)
      Also photos of filming (boom). (LSR Album Accession number 52.)
    - 200-N2, Catskills House, 1980 September; Color 3x5 prints in miniature album. (Box A 90)
      LSR Album Accession number 211.
    - 200-N3, Pocantico (Kykuit) grounds and outdoor sculpture, 1977 November; 10 photos, color 5x7 prints. (Box A 90)
      LSR Album Accession number 1.
    - 200-V1, Woodstock and McDill's garden; JY Ranch, circa 1979 July; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 90)
      MFR at McDill's garden; garden at Mansion (Belvedere); band set up in front of Woodstock Inn; JY pool, MFR on boat, scenery and wildlife. (LSR Album Accession number 216.)
    - 200-W1, JY Ranch, 1940s; Approximately 53 black and white 5x7 photos. (Box A 91)
      MFR, LSR, and children. Scenery, horseback riding, MFR in chaps, camping, hiking, posed pictures. (LSR Album Accession number 3.)
    - 200-W1, JY Ranch, 1959; Mainly color 5x7 prints. (Box A 91)
      Family photos, LSR, MFR, and children, on horseback, cutting wood, etc.; Kykuit; Kent House. Album described as "O" in the album list. (LSR Album Accession number 186.)
    - 200-W2, JY Ranch; Yellowstone, 1940s; Black and white 5x7 prints. (Box A 92)
      Scenery, MFR, daughters; MFR and 2 girls at western train station. (LSR Album Accession number 53.)
    - 200-W3, JY Ranch, 1940s; Black and white 5x7 prints. (Box A 92)
      Family photos, MFR, daughters, LSR, (possibly NAR); horseback riding; scenery. (LSR Album Accession number 54.)
    - 200-W4, JY Ranch, 1976 October; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 93)
      Chapel, moose, MFR and LSR and friends (Lady Bird) and scenery. (LSR Album Accession number 8.)
    - 200-W5, JY Ranch, 1977 September; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 93)
      Moose, friends (including some in album W4), scenery. (LSR Album Accession number 9.)
    - 200-W6, JY Ranch, 1979; Color 3x5 prints, in flip album (Box A 93)
      Moose, friends (Mrs. Bobst), LSR and MFR in scenery, outdoor chapel services; golf; 834 Fifth Avenue, New York. (LSR Album Accession number 57.)
    - 200-W7, JY Ranch in snow, 1980s; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 94)
      LSR, MFR, scenery, MFR on snowmobile. (LSR Album Accession number 58)
    - 200-W8, JY Ranch, 1980 September; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 94)
      Scenery, guests,LSR, MFR, children and grandchildren, flowers. (LSR Album Accession number 61.)
    - 200-W9, JY Ranch, 1981 November and earlier (1950s-1980s); Color 5x7 prints; most date-stamped November 1981 (Box A 94)
      LSR, MFR, family and guests; Armstrong Ranch, King, TX, NAR, circa 1950s (license plate reads NY World's Fair - i.e., 1964)); Bob Hope and LSR, MELEX PGA tournament, ca. 1970s. (LSR Album Accession number 59.)
    - 200-W10, Valley Ranch House, 1982 July; Miniature album with 3x5 color photos. (Box A 94)
      Scenery and construction. (LSR Album Accession number 30.)
    - 200-W11, Valley Ranch House, 1982 July; Color 3x5 shots in 5 1/2 x 6 album. Adhesive tape on page edges deteriorating - some photos flipping loose from pages. (Box A 94)
      Interior and exterior and scenery; LSR in golf cart. (LSR Album Accession number 62.)
  - 300 - Miscellaneous, 1940-1987; 4
    - 300-1, 1940-1980; 58 color 5x7 photos (Box A 95)
      LSR, MFR, ca. 1940; Caribbean cruise, December 1959 (DR property on St. Barts, St. Croix, Barbados, St. Thomas, Caneel); JY Ranch scenery, August 1962; pool at Belvedere, Woodstock, 1959; LSR in Caribbean, August 1960; Union Pacific Trip (LSR and MFR), October 1979; EAL Board meeting, Mexico, October 1979 (LSR); LSR Japan trip, December 1980. (LSR Album Accession number 19.)
    - 300-2, 1959-1973; 64 color 5x7 photos. (Box A 95)
      LSR golfing by ocean, June 1959; (NPS boat?), October 1959; Virgin Islands cruise, December 1959 (St. Croix, St. Thomas, St. Barts, Caneel; LSR-MFR at Hawaii airport, September 1965; Lady Bird Johnson at JY Ranch, September 1965 (with LSR and others); Larry cutting wood at JY; (LSR in Texas); MFR sailing on Rio trip, April 1966; MFR with lei, September 1977; NAR on sailboat, April 1973. (LSR Album Accession number 20.)
    - 300-3, 1963-1973; Color 5x7 prints; album full - some pages buckling on edges. (Box A 96)
      Pocantico, 1963; JY Ranch (woodpile), 1963; Little Dix Bay, April 1964; Cruise to Virgin Islands, October 1963 (NAR and Happy); (Virgin Islands? and guests, August 1964); LSR with 3 men by construction crane, August 1964; JY Ranch, including NAR and Red Mathews, August 1964; Virgin Islands cruise and guests, November 1973 and July 1965. (LSR Album Accession number 205.)
    - 300-4, Soto Grande, Madrid, and Toledo; Palm Springs; JY Ranch, 1976 Christmas - 1977 February, undated; Color 3x5 and 5x7 prints. (Box A 96)
      With friends; MFR on horseback at JY; JY horses. (LSR Album Accession number 202.)
    - 300-5, 1977 September; 22 color 5x7 photos. (Box A 96)
      MFR smelling roses; Golf course and scenery, Hawaii. (LSR Album Accession number 10.)
    - 300-6, Rockefeller Center, 1970s; 6 color 3x5 photos in miniature album. (Box A 97)
      Children playing; skating rink; Atlas and other sculpture. (LSR Album Accession number 67.)
    - 300-7, Charles Browand's 25th-Anniversary Party (of work for the Rockefeller family), 1985 May 29; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 97)
      LSR's chauffeur; party at 30 Rock, Room 5600; LSR, MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 224.)
    - 300-8, Rockefeller Family Office Christmas Party at Big Apple Circus, 1986 December 12; 14 color 5x7 photos; some are coming loose from the pages. (Box A 97)
      DR on elephant, LSR, Abby O'Neill; grandchildren. (LSR Album Accession number 229.)
    - 300-9, Trip to Newport, RI; Chappaquidick; LSR and MFR and grandsons in Tarrytown, 1987 Summer; 24 color 4x6 photos in flip album. Good condition but photos slide out from pages. (Box A 97)
      Croquet game, wedding party, MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 236.)
  - 400 - Civic, 1940s - 1987; 5
    - 400-1, Photos aboard aircraft carrier, 1940s; black and white, 5x7 (Box A 98)
      Includes group photo with LSR (in suit, with camera).(LSR Album Accession number 63.)
    - 400-2, Africa: textile factory; delivery of wild animals for Bronx Zoo., 1950s; black and white, 5 x7,. Album over-filled; some pages buckling. (Box A 98)
      Includes a few LSR, MFR. Also shipboard and airport shots. (LSR Album Accession number 64.)
    - 400-3, Africa: textile factory; animals and scenery, 1950s; black and white, 5x7 (Box A 99)
      Includes MFR. Factory opening. MFR cutting ribbon. Church, school, village scene. (LSR Album Accession number 65.)
    - 400-4, 1963-1975; color, 5x7 (Box A 99)
      YWCA Argentina and Brazil trip (MFR, LSR); Lady Bird, LSR, in Texas; YWCA India, 1963; Alaska (LSR); Woodstock pool with two young boys; Tahiti (LSR, MFR). (LSR Album Accession number 66.)
    - 400-5, Southwest Texas State University, 1976 October 29; Black and white, 5x7 prints. (Box A 100)
      LSR, MFR, Lady Bird Johnson. (LSR Album Accession number 7.)
    - 400-6, Dedication of the Lyndon Baines Johnson Memorial Grove on the Potomac, 1977 October; Color 5x7 prints. Album labeled 1976. (Box A 100)
      LSR, LBJ. See also large album 400-22. (LSR Album Accession number 68.)
    - 400-7, Peter Crisp Twenty-Fifth Anniversary Party (of work with Rockefeller family), 1985 July; Color 5x7 prints. Some yellowing of images; album pages slightly buckled. (Box A 100)
      Party held July 30, 1985, at Room 5600. (Actual anniversary date August 15, 1985.) (LSR Album Accession number 225.)
    - 400-8, Rockefeller Research Laboratories, Ground Breaking Ceremony., 1986 June; Black-and-white 5x7 prints, in tight postbound album (Box A 101)
      MSKCC, June 24, 1986. Address by Vice President George Bush. (LSR Album Accession number 233.)
    - 400-9, Topping Off of the Rockefeller Research Laboratories, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1987 July 1; Black-and-white 5x7 prints. (Box A 101)
      LSR, MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 234.)
  - 500 - Travel, 1940s - 1979; 6
    Albums within the 500, Travel, series are grouped by geographic location: A = Africa, E = Europe, U = United States. In addition, V= Vessels.
    - 500-A1, Africa: Egypt and Belgian Congo, 1950s; Black-and-white 5x7 prints. (Box A 102)
      MFR at Pyramids; fishing, village scenes. (LSR Album Accession number 69.)
    - 500-A2, Africa: Belgian Congo, 1950s; Black-and-white 5x7 prints. (Box A 102)
      Scenery, land, people, animals. MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 70.)
    - 500-E1, Europe: France, Greece, Egypt, 1950s; Black-and-white 5x7 prints. (Box A 103)
      France or Belgium; Pyramids. LSR, MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 71.)
    - 500-E2, Europe: Family Trip, 1956; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 103)
      MFR and children. England, with Mazes; France; river or lake cruise. (LSR Album Accession number 72.)
    - 500-E3, Europe: Norway, Family Trip, 1956; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 104)
      Cruise. Envelope in album with LSR note: Norway - Rauland-Bergen Sculpture Garden '56. (LSR Album Accession number 75.)
    - 500-E4, Europe: Norway, 1974 August; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 104)
      Sea Star trip. With Floyd and Kime Hall. (LSR Album Accession number 74.)
    - 500-E5, Europe: France (Barge Trip); Gibraltar (cruise), 1975 June; Color 5x7 prints. (Box A 105)
      LSR, MFR, friends; yacht cruise - Sea Star. (LSR Album Accession number 73.)
    - 500-E6, Europe: France (Barge Trip); Gibraltar, 1975 June; 8 color 5x7 photos. (Box A 105)
      LSR and scenery. Additional images from barge trip and Gibraltar (see album E5). (LSR Album Accession number 56.)
    - 500-E7, Europe: Italy (Rome); England (Mazes' cottage in Sussex), 1979 May; 54 images. Color, mainly 5x7 prints. (Box A 105)
      LSR, MFR, unidentified; Paul and Jessie Maze, Mill Cottage. (LSR Album Accession number 22.)
    - 500-E8, Europe: Greece (Aegean Cruise), 1979 April; Color 5x7 prints. Tags numbering photos are falling off. (Box A 106)
      LSR, MFR, with (Lady Bird Johnson and Lynda Robb?). Including Delos. (LSR Album Accession number 23.)
    - 500-E9, Europe: Greece (Aegean Cruise), 1979 April; Color 5x7 prints. Tags numbering photos are falling off. (Box A 106)
      Some places identified. LSR, MFR, and group. (LSR Album Accession number 24.)
    - 500-E10, Europe: Greece (Aegean Cruise), 1979 April; Color 5x7 prints. Tags numbering photos are falling off. (Box A 107)
      Some places identified. LSR, MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 25.)
    - 500-E11, Europe: Greece (Aegean Cruise), 1979 April; Color 5x7 prints. Tags numbering photos are falling off. (Box A 107)
      Mykenos, Crete, Delphi. LSR, MFR. (LSR Album Accession number 26.)
    - 500-U1, United States: Florida, Indiana (EAL), Bahamas, 1940s-1950s; Black-and-white 5x7 prints. (Box A 108)
      Florida (and Indiana?) trip associated with EAL meeting. Rickenbacker, fishing, horserace, Rickenbacker and LSR on beach; EAL hanger; MFR in (Bahamas), Porcupine Club. (LSR Album Accession number 16.)
    - 500-U2, United States: EAL Board Meeting (New York); Florida; Hudson River; Abby Rockefeller Mauze's house in Bermuda, 1950s; Black-and-white 5x7 prints, and 2 color prints at end. (Box A 108)
      Includes MFR sunning on board ship, Florida; MFR and children at beach; children on board ship fishing; woman (possibly MFR) painting, canoeing. (LSR Album Accession number 6.)
    - 500-V1, Vessels: Dauntless (Hudson River, New York City skyline), 1940s-1950s; Black-and-white 5x7 prints; 7 later color photos of Dauntless model. (Box A 109)
      Includes LSR, MFR, crew, and friends (watching regatta). Added at end, photographs of model of Dauntless, sent to LSR by A. A. Richardson, 1980, with note. (LSR Album Accession number 4.)
    - 500-V2, Vessels: Dauntless; Sea Beast, 1940s-1950s; Black-and-white 5x7 prints. Some photos out of order (Box A 109)
      Children in pool; LSR and MFR christening the Dauntless; LSR and party duck-hunting; salvage of Sea Beast; Whirl Wind; unidentified on boat with LSR. (LSR Album Accession number 76.)
    - 500-V3, Vessels: Dauntless, 1978 February; Mainly color 5x7 prints. (Box A 109)
      Lloyd's Register of American Yachts page copied at front; includes shots of crew. (LSR Album Accession number 78.)
  - 600 - Resorts, 1950s - 1978; 7
    Albums within the 600, Resorts, series are grouped by resort: Ca = Caneel Bay, Ce = Cerromar Beach, D = Dorado Beach, L = Little Dix Bay, M = Mauna Kea, S = Saint Croix.
    - 600-Ca-1, Caribbean cruise; Texas?, 1950s; Approximately 75 black and white 5x7 photos, in full album. (Box A 110)
      MFR and LSR on yacht and beach; Caneel Bay; Kingston, Jamaica, seaplane; livestock; Winthrop Rockefeller, NAR and WR on horseback - Texas (LSR Album Accession number 5.)
    - 600-Ca-2, Caneel Bay, Peter Island, Dorado Beach, 1954; 84 color 5x7 photos, in full album. (Box A 110)
      Construction and scenery; including MFR, NAR, and others; spearfishing. (LSR Album Accession number 12.)
    - 600-Ca-3, Caneel Bay, 1978 February; Approximately 21 color 5x7 photos. 3 photos out for Fred Smith book. (Box A 111)
      Sunsets, sailboat, and views. (LSR Album Accession number 13.)
    - 600-Ca-4, Caneel Bay and Little Dix Bay?, 1980 March; Full album of 5x7 color photos. (Box A 111)
      Mainly Little Dix; a few photos at end of LSR and 834 Fifth Ave terrace. (LSR Album Accession number 77.)
    - 600-Ce-1 (copy 2), Cerromar Beach Hotel, 1978 June; 21 5x7 color photos. Album carded as large album, but it does not seem to be. (Box A 111)
      PR photos, interiors, exteriors, scenery, guests. (LSR Album Accession number 55.) Album is supposed to be a duplicate of Album 175 (600-Ce-1, copy 1), not found. Both albums were originally indexed as part of the Large albums series.
    - 600-D1, Dorado Beach Hotel, 1987 April; Small album of 4x6 color photos. (Box A 112)
      Album of photographs taken by Harmon Goldstone and sent to LSR, May 11, 1987. Interiors and exteriors of Dorado Beach Hotel resort. (LSR Album Accession number 232.)
    - 600-D1 (copy 2), Dorado Beach Hotel, 1978 June; 52 color 5x7 photos. (Box A 112)
      PR photos, scenery, flowers, interior and exterior facilities and grounds. (LSR Album Accession number 14.) Duplicate of large album 600-D1 (accession number 173).
    - 600-L1, Little Dix Bay, 1978 February; Color 5x7 photos. Some photos out for Fred Smith book. (Box A 112)
      Sailboats (Evening Star and unknown)and scenery, MFR and guests. Photo of Queen Elizabeth II supposed to be in album, but not found. (LSR Album Accession number 204.)
    - 600-L2, Little Dix Bay, 1978 February; Approximately 37 color 5x7 photos. (Box A 112)
      PR and personal photos; includes Evening Star, MFR with guests, (possibly Wes Frye). (LSR Album Accession number 18.)
    - 600-L2 (copy 2), Little Dix Bay, 1978 February; Album is intact (includes photos missing from album L2). 5x7 color photos (Box A 113)
      Exactly duplicates photos in small album L2. (LSR Album Accession number 214.)
    - 600-M1, Mauna Kea, 1965 November; 3 x 5 color photos. (Box A 113)
      Hotel grounds and staff, entertainment; LSR, MFR, and guests; golf, horseback riding. (LSR Album Accession number 78.)
    - 600-M2, Mauna Kea, 1968 March; 24 color 3x5 photos in ring-binder album with flip stacked photos. Condition okay, but consider removing from album - acidic, and space considerations. (Box A 113)
      Artistic photos of scenery, grounds, interiors, ocean, golf course, artwork, birds and flowers. (LSR Album Accession number 84.)
    - 600-M3, Mauna Kea, 1977 October; Color 5x7 photos. (Box A 114)
      Artistic PR photos; card indicates album contains duplicates of large PR photos. Scenery, buildings, staff, artwork, general guests. (LSR Album Accession number 79.)
    - 600-M4, Mauna Kea, 1977 September; Color 5x7 photos. (Box A 114)
      Buildings, grounds, scenery; includes MFR, Wes Frye on boat. (LSR Album Accession number 82.)
    - 600-M5, Mauna Kea, 1977-1978 March; Color 5x7 photos. (Box A 114)
      Mauna Kea scenery, golf course, boats; 1 photo of Wes Frye and others, March 1978. (LSR Album Accession number 81.)
    - 600-M6, Mauna Kea, 1977-1978 March; Color 5x7 photos. (Box A 115)
      MFR with floral arrangement; scenery, flora, golf course, ocean and boats. (LSR Album Accession number 83.)
    - 600-M7, Mauna Kea, 1978 March; Color 5x7 photos. (Box A 115)
      Card indicates Vol. 1. Professional photos of grounds and landscape (no people). Note: includes pointsettia used on Christmas card. (LSR Album Accession number 80.)
    - 600-M8, Mauna Kea, 1978 March; Color 5x7 photos. (Box A 115)
      Card indicates Vol. 2. LSR and MFR and guests. Grounds, scenery, artwork, beach and sailboats. (LSR Album Accession number 21.)
    - 600-S1, Saint Croix, 1978 June; Color 5x7 photos. (Box A 116)
      PR photos (by Davis); duplicates of photos in large album (accession number 178). Landscape, scenery, golf course, buildings, fort, port, etc. (LSR Album Accession number 15; indexed with the large album series.)